# **Serhat Yavuzyigit**

### Research And Development Intern

Ankara, TURKEY

soyavuzyigit@gmail.com

(+90) 506 336 95 24

github.com/serhatyavuzyigit

Motivated student completing Computer Engineering degree. Gained experience with two long term internships in software development and currently doing a long term internship in a research role. Experienced in Agile and Scrum environments. Supports team members with the project, design and programming needs. Fluent in English and Turkish. Want to contribute to the world for became a better place.



#### **EDUCATION**

# <sup>2016-09</sup> - Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering

TOBB University of Economics And Technology - Ankara, TURKEY

- Graduated with 3.07/4.00 GPA
- Courses Taken: Data Structres, Algorithms, Software Engineering, Computer Graphics, Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, Operating Systems, Database Systems...



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 2020-09 - Research And Development Intern

**Current** ESEN, Ankara, TURKEY

 I am currently working with Research And Development team on Computer Vision and Deep Learning.

# 2019-09 - Software Engineer Intern 2019-12

AYESAS, Ankara, TURKEY

- Worked with a software engineering project team.
- Gained experience with avionics software development and Microsoft Visual Studio environment.
- Developed a tool using C++ and QT.

## 2019-01 - Software Engineer Intern

SimBT, Ankara, TURKEY

- Worked with a scrum team in defence industry software engineering project.
- Contributed to project with solving bugfixes, making improvements and refactoring the code.
- Gained experience with Java, JavaFX, Git and Maven.



### **SKILLS**

- Software Development
- Algorithms and Data Structures
- Java, C, C++, Python, JavaScript,
  OpenGL Programming



- Machine Learning / Deep Learning
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Science
- Sports



### **PROJECTS**

 You can see my programming projects and code snippets on my github page